A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1984-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1984-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.871
This collection consists of 14,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1987 July 10.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general and admistrative committee files, 1984-1985; and, permanent files [1939] 1955-1987.
Permanent records concern: Center for Advanced Studies, Capital Campaign Solicitations; Miller Center; and the Endowment Fund.
Organization
Series I: General Files, 1984-1985 Boxes 1-22
Series II: Administrative Committees Files, 1984-1985 Boxes 22-24
Series III: Permanent Files[1939] 1955-1987 Boxes 24-49
Series IV: Restricted Material, 1984-1985 Box 50
Contents List
- Series I: General Records
  - "A" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Administration 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing Services 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--General 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--Law 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--Medical 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs--Woodson Institute 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association--General 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - American Council on Education 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Annual Report--President (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Anthropology 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Architecture 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Art--General 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Art--Bayly Museum 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Asian Studies 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Associated Western Universities 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Colleges 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Universities (1-5 of 6) 1984-1985 (Box 3)
  - Association of American Universities (6 of 6) 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Astronomy 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Athletics--General 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Athletics--ACC 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Athletics--CFA 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Athletics--Finances (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Athletics--NCAA (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Attorney General--State 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - Auditor--Internal (3 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - "B" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Biology--General (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Business and Finance--General 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Business and Finance--Executive Planning Group 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Business Operations (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Cavalier Daily 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (1 of 2) 1984-1985 (Box 6)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (2 of 2) 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Charlottesville, City of 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Chemistry 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Civil Rights--General 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Classics 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Clinch Valley College--General 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - College Board 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Commerce--General 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Community Colleges (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Comptroller--State (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Congress 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Consortia--General (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Consortia--Central Virginia (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Consortia--Northern Virginia 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Consortia--Tidewater 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Consortia-Valley 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Consortia--Western 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Continuing Education 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Council of Presidents 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Council on Southern Universities (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - "D" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Darden School 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Darden School Sponsors 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Deans Meetings 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Development--General 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Drama--General 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - "E" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Economics 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Education 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Energy Policies Study Center (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Engineering and Applied Science 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Engineering and Buildings 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - English 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Enrollment--General 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Environmental Sciences (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Equal Opportunity Office 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - "F" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Faculty--General 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Food Services 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - French 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - "G" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly--House Appropriations 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - General Assembly--Legislative 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - General Services 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - German 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Gifts and Grants (3 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Government Relations 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--General 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--Administration 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--Commerce and Resources 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--Education 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--Finances 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--Human Resources 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--Task Force on Science and Technology 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--Transportation and Public Safety (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Governor--Washington Liaison Office 1984-1985 (Box 10)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences--Career Opportunities Institute 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - "H" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education of 1965 (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education--Title I (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education--Title III (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education--Title IV (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Higher Education--Title IX (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - History 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Honor System 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Honor System--Olden Polynice--Incoming (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Honor System--Olden Polynice--Outgoing 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Housing 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Information Technology 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Institute of Government 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs (empty) 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - International Students 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - "J" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Law--General 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Lawn Society 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Legal Advisors Office 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Library 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - "M" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Marine Science 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Mariner's Museum (3 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Material Management 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Mathematics 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--General 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Hospital 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Hospital Personnel 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Medical School 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Medical Center--Medical School Personnel 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Medical Center--Nursing 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Miller Center (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Music 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (1 of 2) 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (2 of 2) 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - National Science Foundation 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Newcomb Hall 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - "P" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Parking and Transportation 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Personnel--General 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Personnel and Training 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Philosophy 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Physical Planning 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Physical Plant 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Physics 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Planning--Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Planning and Budget--Capital Outlay 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Planning and Budget--State (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Planning and Budget--University 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Promotions 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Provost 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Provost--Associate for Research 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Psychology 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Purchase and Supply 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - "R" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Real Estate, Risk Management, and Safety 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Recommendations A-Z 1984-1985 (Box 17)
  - Registrar 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Religious Studies 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - ROTC--General 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - ROTC--Army 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - ROTC--Navy 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (5 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Senate--University 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Sociology 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Southern Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Spanish, Italian, and Portuguese 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Sponsored Programs 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHE) (3 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - SCHE--Council Notes 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - State Department of Education 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Student Affairs (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Student Council--General 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Student Council--Minutes 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Travel Invoices 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Treasurer 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - U.S. Savings Bonds 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - United Way 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - Universities Research Association 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Journal 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Police 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Press of Virginia 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Relations 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - University Union 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - "W" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - "X, Y, Z" Miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box 22)
- Series II: Administrative Committees
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Telephone (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Telephone Agreement (1980) 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - General 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Admissions 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Afro-American Affairs Advisory 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Arboretum and Landscape 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Architectural Advisory 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Athletic Advisory 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Bayly Museum 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Calendar 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Cemetery 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Chapel 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Chemical and Biological Hazards Safety--Subcommittee--DNA 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Commencement and Convocation--Subcommittee--Processions 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittee--Public Occasions 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Community Colleges 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Computers 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Education and Employment Opportunities 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Energy Conservation 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Fraternities and Sororities 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Fulbright Grants 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Graphics 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Gwathmey Award 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Housing 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - International Students 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Jefferson Award 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Lectures--Page, Barbour, and Richards 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Library 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Master Plan 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Names 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Proxy Advisory 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Radiation Safety--Subcommittee--Radioactive Drug Research 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Registration 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Residential Life 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Rhodes Scholarship 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - ROTC 1984-1985 (Box 23)
  - Scheduling 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Loans 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Security and General Safety 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Student Activities 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Student Health 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Summer Grants 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Summer Session 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Traffic Appeals 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Traffic and Parking 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Truman Scholarships 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - University Committee on Students 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - University Press 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - University Union and Student Activities Building 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1984-1985 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1984-1985 (Box 24)
- Series III: Permanent Files
  - Board of Visitors--Lists and Organizations 1955-1958 (Box 24)
  - Board of Visitors-General (3 folders) 1982 Jul-1983 Jun (Box 24)
  - Board of Visitors-General (4 folders) 1983 Jul-1985 Jul (Box 25)
  - Board of Visitors--Barrett, C. Waller 1969 Feb-1979 Feb (Box 25)
  - Board of Visitors--Barrett, C. Waller--Tenure 1974 Oct-1977 Aug (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Battle, William C. 1976 Mar-1980 Mar (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Bufford, Robert P. 1972 May-1980 Feb (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Cunningham, C. Clarke 1980 Feb-1984 May (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Dudley, William M. 1976 Mar-1984 Mar (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--French, Warren B., Jr. 1972 Mar-1980 Mar (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Harvey, William R. 1982 Mar-1986 Mar (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Hatcher, Robert V., Jr. 1979 Feb-1986 Nov (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Ingrassia, Timothy J. 1985 May-1986 Mar (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Leggett, William E. 1972 Apr-1980 Feb (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Montague, David N. 1980 Feb-1984 Mar (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Perry, Ferman W. 1980 Feb-1984 Apr (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Updike, Dr. Glenn B., Jr. 1979 Feb-1983 Apr (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Valentine, Massie 1979 Feb-1987 Jan (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Wade, Neal O., Jr. 1982 Mar-1987 May (Box 26)
  - Board of Visitors--Whitehead, Gregory C. 1984 Jun-Jul (Box 27)
  - Board of Visitors--Willis, Gordon F. 1983 Jun-1984 Oct (Box 27)
  - Capital Campaign--General (2 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 27)
  - Capital Campaign--Case for Private Gifts 1982-1985 (Box 27)
  - Capital Campaign--Case Statement 1982-1985 (Box 27)
  - Capital Campaign--Case Statement Brochures 1982-1985 (Box 27)
  - Capital Campaign--Position Letter #1 1982-1985 (Box 27)
  - Capital Campaign--Position Letter #2-4 (3 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 28)
  - Capital Campaign--Final Letter and Responses 1982-1985 (Box 28)
  - Capital Campaign---Position Letters Mailing List 1982-1985 (Box 28)
  - Capital Campaign--Committees 1982-1985 (Box 28)
  - Capital Campaign--Medical Center Development Committee 1982-1985 (Box 28)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "A" 1982-1985 (Box 28)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "B" (3 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 29)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "C" (1-2 of 3) 1982-1985 (Box 29)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "C" (3 of 3) 1982-1985 (Box 30)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "D" (2 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 30)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "E" 1982-1985 (Box 30)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "F" 1982-1985 (Box 30)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "G" (1 of 2) 1982-1985 (Box 30)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "G" (2 of 2) 1982-1985 (Box 31)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "H" (2 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 31)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "I-Jo" 1982-1985 (Box 31)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "Ju-K" 1982-1985 (Box 31)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "L" 1982-1985 (Box 31)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "M" (3 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 32)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "N-O" 1982-1985 (Box 32)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "P-Ph" 1982-1985 (Box 32)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "Pi-Q" 1982-1985 (Box 33)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "R" 1982-1985 (Box 33)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "S" (3 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 33)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "T" (2 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 34)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "W-Wh" 1982-1985 (Box 34)
  - Capital Campaign--Solicitation, Pledges, Prospects "Wi-Z" 1982-1985 (Box 34)
  - Alumni Association--Medical 1974-1983 (Box 35)
  - Animal Control Office 1973-1979 (Box 35)
  - Athletics--General (2 folders) 1978-1982 (Box 35)
  - Athletics--Bestwick 1975-1983 (Box 35)
  - Athletics--Form Letters 1978 (Box 35)
  - Athletics--Report for President 1978 (Box 36)
  - Biology--Blandy Farm (2 folders) 1964-1987 (Box 36)
  - Birdwood--General Information (2 folders) 1966-1980 (Box 36)
  - Center for Advanced Studies 1975-1985 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Advisory Board II and Appointments 1965-1985 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Membership (2 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Reports 1975-1982 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Administration of Arts and Sciences 1978 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Bayly Museum 1984-1985 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Commerce 1981 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Darden School 1979 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Drama, Music 1979-1980 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Education 1980 (Box 37)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Engineering 1979 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--English 1980 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Environmental Sciences 1978-1985 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Foreign Languages 1979 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Government and Foreign Affairs 1986 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee----Law 1983 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Library 1979 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Nursing 1980 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Pharmacology 1979 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Physics 1976-1984 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Physiology 1975-1977 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Religious Studies 1980-1981 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Research Enterprise 1980-1982 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--Sociology 1985 (Box 38)
  - Center for Advanced Studies--Visiting Committee--University Press 1985 (Box 38)
  - Council of Presidents--Task Force on Decentralization (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 39)
  - Duncan, Andrew ( 2 folders) 1968-1982 (Box 39)
  - Emergency Plan 1985 (Box 39)
  - Eminent Scholars (1 of 2) 1975-1981 (Box 39)
  - Eminent Scholars (2 of 2) 1975-1981 (Box 40)
  - Endowment Fund--General (2 folders) 1973-1981 (Box 40)
  - Endowment Fund--Financial Reports (1 of 2) 1974-1985 (Box 40)
  - Endowment Fund--Financial reports (2 of 2) 1974-1985 (Box 41)
  - Endowment Fund--Lambeth Colonnades 1976 (Box 41)
  - Endowment Fund--President's Contingent Fund (2 folders) 1972-1986 (Box 41)
  - Endowment Fund--Teaching Award (1 of 2) 1975-1986 (Box 41)
  - Endowment Fund--Teaching Award (2 of 2) 1975-1985 (Box 42)
  - Engineering and Building--Directives (3 folders) 1979-1986 (Box 42)
  - Equal Opportunity Employment (EOE)--Affirmative Action V (1 of 3) 1984-1986 (Box 42)
  - Equal Opportunity Employment (EOE)--Affirmative Action (2-3 of 3) 1984-1986 (Box 43)
  - Faculty Tenure 1969-1985 (Box 43)
  - Heald, Hobson and Associates--Administration Study 1967 (Box 43)
  - Historic Central Grounds 1976-1977 (Box 43)
  - Institutional Purpose 1964 (Box 43)
  - Kenan Charitable Fund 1967-1984 (Box 43)
  - Library Historical 1939-1960 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center--Health Services Foundation (2 folders) 1979-1982 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center--Replacement Hospital (1 of 2) 1982-1984 (Box 44)
  - Medical Center--Replacement Hospital (2 of 2) 1982-1984 (Box 45)
  - Minority Affairs (3 folders) 1980-1986 (Box 45)
  - Monroe Papers 1967-1973 (Box 45)
  - Patent Foundation (2 folders) 1978-1985 (Box 46)
  - Physics (SURA) (3 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 46)
  - Pratt, John Lee (2 folders) 1975-1984 (Box 47)
  - Pratt, John Lee--Newspaper Clippings 1975-1976 (Box 47)
  - Records Management 1963-1978 (Box 47)
  - Religious Organizations (Chapel History) 1966-1970 (Box 47)
  - Salaries (1 of 2) 1974-1983 (Box 47)
  - Salaries (2 of 2) 1974-1983 (Box 48)
  - Sigma Chi 1982-1986 (Box 48)
  - Self-Study 1974-1975 (Box 48)
  - Self-Study--Committee (1 of 2) 1971-1976 (Box 48)
  - Self-Study--Committee (2 of 2) 1971-1976 (Box 49)
  - Self-Study--Report 1973-1981 (Box 49)
  - South Africa (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 49)
- Series IV: Restricted Material
  - Restricted Material (2 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 50)